<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on SARK</title>
    <link>http://example.org/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on SARK</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 20:51:35 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://example.org/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Pharaon - Stereo Speaker Sound System</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/pharaon/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 20:51:35 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/pharaon/</guid>
      <description>This speaker was about building something that would catch your eye and make you wonder about it&amp;rsquo;s purpose, without compromising on sound quality.
The speakers are built out of plywood and MDF. They were then covered in oak.
The setup uses 7 membranes in total (1 subwoofer, 2 woofers, 2 mediums, 2 tweeters). The subwoofer is powered by a 150 Watt amplifier.
If you plan to get one of those, make sure to warn your neighbors beforehand!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Drops - Modular Dining Pendant lamp</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/drops/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 20:14:11 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/drops/</guid>
      <description>The concept for drops came while thinking of building a version of Photon (my other pendant lamp) that would be modular. Here is the result:
Each &amp;ldquo;droplet&amp;rdquo; consists of a module that supports an LED. Similarly to Photon, the light can shine directly onto the surface but is also reflected to the ceiling by the reflector beneath the LED. Here is what a module looks like:
The aluminum block that holds the LED also serves as a heat sink.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FPV Drone</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/drone/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 20:14:11 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/drone/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MotionPilot - FPV Drone Motion Controller</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/motionpilot/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 20:14:11 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/motionpilot/</guid>
      <description>The goal of this product was to improve the flight experience with First Person View (FPV) drones. This was achieved by redefining how an FPV drone is controlled by introducing motion control and by designing the UI specifically for FPV.
This project has been challenging and incredibly rewarding. It involved designing multiple prototypes, designing and testing software, electronics and mechanical systems. We manufactured and assembled more than hundreds of prototypes that are still used by our beta-testers to this day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Photon - Dining Pendant lamp</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/photon/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 20:14:11 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/photon/</guid>
      <description>This lamp started off with a beam of wood. A thin plate of stainless steel floats just under it. The six LEDs that are placed throughout the beam shine a warm light towards the table. Photon also provides a soft ambiance illumination as the light reflects on the steel towards the ceiling and the lamp&amp;rsquo;s sides through the gap between the metal and the wood.
The sheets of metal are laser cut.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stack - Modular Shelving System</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/stack/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 20:14:11 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/stack/</guid>
      <description>Stack is a shelving system that consists of a combination of slotted boards of wood and threaded rods.
By selecting the board dimensions, the number of boards, the number of supporting rods and the threaded rod height, the user can design a shelf specific to his needs.
For lower shelves, the slots can be replaced with holes. This makes the assembly process more tedious as the nuts have to be threaded all the way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Steel - Big Floor Lamp</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/steel/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 20:14:11 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/steel/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wind Turbine - Home Electricity Generation</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/turbine/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 20:14:11 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/turbine/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Example Post</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/my-first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2022 23:44:29 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/my-first-post/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Photon is a lamp. Duh!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
